JEHANZEB KHAN, M.S.

Mobile: (832) 455-8318

Email: JehanzebKh4n@gmail.com

54 Webb Creek Place The Woodlands, TX, 77382

CAREER PROFILE

Highly motivated candidate who has proven to thrive under fast-paced and challenging environments. Past experiences and education has led to the development of indispensable skills such as analyzing and problem solving, critical thinking, technical writing and managing and articulating complex subjects.

EXPERIENCE

Student Desktop Support Engineer/Technician at IT@SAM Sam Houston State University, Huntsville, TX

July 2022 - Current

- Took in an average of 10 calls per day consisting of emergency and regular calls in managing desktop support issues from students, faculty and staff.
- Created and managed an average of 10 tickets per day.
- Completed and resolved tickets more efficiently than 3 other co-workers.
- Troubleshooted software and device issues for classrooms.
- Managed the computer lab ensuring printers and computers were functioning properly.

Intern

UNLV School of Dental Medicine, Las Vegas, NV

July 2017 - August 2017

- Utilized Dentrix software to document medical records and conducted interviews with new patients.
- Developed a strong rapport and assisted the program director of the general practice residency with administrative and clinical duties.
- Intern

University of Maryland School of Dentistry, Baltimore, MD

October 2017 - November 2017

- Exceeded expectations by providing quality customer service experience by addressing all clients concerns and questions in a timely manner.
- Collaborated with the 70 faculty and staff to gain a foundational knowledge of procedures and practices.

Intern

Baylor College of Medicine & Ben Taub Hospital, Houston, TX

June 2015 - August 2016

- Assisted with data entry and record keeping of confidential patient data using eClinicalWorks software.
- Increased operational efficiency by ensuring the exam room was cleaned and prepared for each appointment.

Intern

Acclaimed Heart and Vascular Center, Spring, TX

August for 2012 - 2014

- Managed patient intake in a fast-paced environment and reviewed medical records using eClinicalWorks software.
- Assisted in new patient interviews and documented their information with eClinicalWorks software.

Graduate Researcher

The University of Texas School of Dentistry at Houston, Houston Texas

January - August 2018

- Led a team of 5 researchers in organizing and conducting research team meetings.
- Gathered and analyzed data for managerial review and further testing.

EDUCATION

Sam Houston State University, Huntsville, TX
Bachelor of Business Administration Management Information Systems

December 2023

Tulane School of Medicine, New Orleans, LA Master of Science in Anatomy

May 2020

Baylor University, Waco, TX
Bachelor of Science Biochemistry

December 2016